<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Drivme</string>
    <string name="underline_text_fp"><u>Forgot Password?</u></string>
    <string name="underline_text_signup"><u>Sign Up</u></string>
    <string name="underline_text_login"><u>Login</u></string>
    <string name="underline_text_joinus"><u>Join Us</u></string>
    <string name="underline_text_resend"><u>Resend OTP</u></string>

    <string name="user_agreement">Last updated August 22, 2022

\n\nDrivme is licensed to You (End-User) by Drivme Co., Ltd., located and registered at 123, Anywhere Road, Any City, Penang 123456, Malaysia (\'Licensor), for use only under the terms of this License Agreement.

\n\nBy downloading the Licensed Application from Google\'s software distribution platform (\'Play Store\'), and any update thereto (as permitted by this License Agreement), You indicate that You agree to be bound by all the terms and conditions of this License Agreement, and that You accept this License Agreement Play Store is referred to in this License Agreement as \'Services\'.

\n\nThe parties of this License Agreement acknowledge that the Services are not a Party to this License Agreement and are not bound by any provisions or obligations regarding the Licensed Application, such as warranty, liability, maintenance, and support thereof. Drivme Co., Ltd, not the Services, is solely responsible for the Licensed Application and the content thereof.

\n\nThis License Agreement may not provide for usage rules for the Licensed Application that conflict with the latest Google Play Terms of Service (\'Usage Rules\'). Drivme Co., Ltd acknowledges that it had the opportunity to review the usage Rules and this License Agreement is not conflicting with them.

\n\nDrivme when purchased or downloaded through the Services, is licensed to You for use only under the terms of this License Agreement. The Licensor reserves all rights not expressly granted to You. Drivme is to be used on devices that operate with Google\'s operating system (\'Android\').

\n\nTABLE OF CONTENTS
\n1. THE APPLICATION
\n2. SCOPE OF LICENSE
\n3. TECHNICAL REQUIREMENTS
\n4. MAINTENANCE AND SUPPORT
\n5. USES OF DATA
\n6. USER-GENERATED CONTRIBUTIONS
\n7. CONTRIBUTION LICENSE
\n8. LIABILITY
\n9. WARRANTY
\n10. PRODUCT CLAIMS
\n11. LEGAL COMPLIANCES
\n12. TERMINATION
\n13. THIRD-PARTY TERMS OF AGREEMENTS AND BENEFICIARY
\n14. INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS
\n15. APPLICABLE LAW
\n16. MISCELLANEOUS
\n17. CONTACT US

\n\n1. THE APPLICATION
\nDrivme (\'Licensed Application\') is a piece of software created to Driver Hiring — and customised for Android mobile devices (\'Devices\'). It is used to hire a driver.

\n\n2. SCOPE OF LICENSE
\n2.1 This License will also govern any updates of the Licensed Application provided by Licensor that replace, repair, and/or supplement the first Licensed Application, unless a separate License is provided tor such update, in which case the terms of that new License will govern.
\n2.2 You may not snare or make the Licensed Application available to third parties (unless to the degree allowed by the usage Rules, and with Drivme Co., Ltd.’s prior written consent), sell, rent, lend, lease, or otherwise redistribute the Licensed Application.
\n2.3 You may not reverse engineer, translate, disassemble, integrate, decompile, remove, modify, combine, create derivative works or updates of, adapt, or attempt to derive the source code of the Licensed Application, or any part thereof (except with Drivme Co., Ltd.’s prior written consent).
\n2.4 You may not copy (excluding when expressly authorised by this License and the Usage Rules) or alter the Licensed Application or portions thereof. You may create and store copies only on devices that You own or control for backup keeping under the terms of this License, the usage Rules, and any other terms and conditions that apply to the device or software used. You may not remove any intellectual property notices. You acknowledge that no unauthorised third parties may gain access to these copies at any time. It you sell your Devices to a third party; you must remove the Licensed Application from the Devices before doing so.
\n2.5 Violations of the obligations mentioned above, as well as the attempt of such infringement, may be subject to prosecution and damages.
\n2.6 Licensor reserves the right to modify the terms and conditions of licensing.
\n2.7 Nothing in this License should be interpreted to restrict third-party terms. When using the Licensed Application, You must ensure that You comply with applicable third-party terms and conditions.

\n\n3. TECHNICAL REQUIREMENTS
\n3.1 The Licensed Application requires a firmware version 1.0.0 or higher. Licensor recommends using the latest version of the firmware.
\n3.2 Licensor attempts to keep the Licensed Application updated so that it complies with modified/new versions of the firmware and new hardware. You are not granted rights to claim such an update
\n3.3 You acknowledge that it is Your responsibility to confirm and determine that the app end-user device on which You intend to use the Licensed Application satisfies the technical specifications mentioned above.
\n3.4 Licensor reserves the right to modify the technical specifications as it sees appropriate at any time

\n\n4. MAINTENANCE AND SUPPORT
\n4.1 The Licensor is solely responsible for providing any maintenance and support services for this Licensed Application. You can reach the Licensor at the email address listed in the Play Store Overview for this Licensed Application.
\n4.2 Drivme Co., Ltd and the End-User acknowledge that the Services have no obligation whatsoever to furnish any maintenance and support services with respect to the Licensed Application.

\n\n5. USES OF DATA
\nYou acknowledge that Licensor will be able to access and adjust Your downloaded Licensed Application content and Your personal information, and that Licensors use of such material and information is subject to Your legal agreements with Licensor and Licensors privacy policy, which can be accessed by Click on the Privacy Policy icon.

\n\nYou acknowledge that the Licensor may periodically collect and use technical data and related information about your device, system, and application software, and peripherals, offer product support facilitate the software updates, and for purposes of providing other services to you (it any) related to the Licensed Application. Licensor may also use this information to improve its products or to provide services or technologies to you if it is in a form that does not personally identify you.

\n\n6. USER-GENERATED CONTRIBUTIONS
\nThe Licensed Application may invite you to chat, contribute to, or participate in blogs, message boards, online forums, and other functionality, and may provide you with the opportunity to create, submit, post, display, transmit, perform, publish, distribute, or broadcast content and materials to us or in the Licensed Application, including but not limited to text, writings, video, audio, photographs, graphics, comments, suggestions, or personal information or other material (collectively, \'Contributions\'). Contributions may be viewable by other users of the Licensed Application and through third-party websites or applications such as, any Contributions you transmit may be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. When you create or make available any Contributions, you thereby represent and warrant that:

\n\n• The creation, distribution, transmission, public display, or performance, and the accessing, downloading, or copying of your Contributions do not and will not infringe the proprietary rights, including but not limited to the copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret, or moral rights of any third party.
\n• You are the creator and owner of or have the necessary Licenses, rights, consents, releases, and permissions to use and to authorise us, the Licensed Application, and other users of the Licensed Application to use your Contributions in any manner contemplated by the Licensed Application and this License Agreement.
\n• You have the written consent release, and/or permission of each and every identifiable individual person in your Contributions to use the name or likeness or each and every such identifiable individual person to enable inclusion and use of your Contributions in any manner contemplated by the Licensed Application and this License Agreement
\n• Your Contributions are not false, inaccurate, or misleading.
\n• Your Contributions are not unsolicited or unauthorised advertising, promotional materials, pyramid schemes, chain letters, spam, mass mailings, or other forms of solicitation.
\n• Your Contributions are not obscene, lewd, lascivious, filthy, violent, harassing libellous, slanderous, or otherwise objectionable (as determined by us).
\n• Your Contributions do not ridicule, mock, disparage, intimidate, or abuse anyone.
\n• Your Contributions are not used to harass or threaten (in the legal sense of those terms) any other person and to promote violence against a specific person or class of people.
\n• Your Contributions do not violate any applicable law, regulation, or rule
\n• Your Contributions do not violate the privacy or publicity rights of any third party.
\n• Your Contributions do not violate any applicable law concerning child pornography, or otherwise intended to protect the health or well-being of minors.
\n• Your Contributions do not include any offensive comments that are connected to race, national origin, gender, sexual preference, or physical handicap.
\n• Your Contributions do not otherwise violate, or link to material that violates, any provision of this License Agreement, or any applicable law or regulation.

\n\nAny use of the Licensed Application in violation of the foregoing violates this License Agreement and may result in, among other things, termination, or suspension of your rights to use the Licensed Application.

\n\n7. CONTRIBUTION LICENSE
\nBy posting your Contributions to any part of the Licensed Application or making Contributions accessible to the Licensed Application by linking your account from the Licensed Application to any of your social networking accounts, you automatically grant, and you represent and warrant that you have the right to grant, to us an unrestricted, unlimited, irrevocable, perpetual, non-exclusive, transferable, royalty-tree, fully-paid, worldwide right, and License to host use copy, reproduce, disclose sell, resell, publish, broad cast, retitle, archive, store, cache, publicly display, reformat, translate, transmit, excerpt (in whole or in part), and distribute such Contributions (including without limitation, your image and voice) tor any purpose, commercial advertising, or otherwise, and to prepare derivative works of, or incorporate in other works, such as Contributions, and grant and authorise sublicenses of the foregoing. The use and distribution may occur in any media formats and through any media channels.

\n\nThis License will apply to any form, media, or technology now known or hereafter developed, and includes our use of your name, company name, and franchise name, as applicable, and any of the trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos, and personal and commercial images you provide. You waive all moral rights in your Contributions, and you warrant that moral rights have not otherwise been asserted in your Contributions.

\n\nWe do not assert any ownership over your Contributions. You retain full ownership of all your Contributions and any intellectual property rights, or other proprietary rights associated with your Contributions. We are not liable for any statements or representations in your Contributions provided by you in any area in the Licensed Application. You are solely responsible for your Contributions to the Licensed Application, and you expressly agree to exonerate us from any and all responsibility and to retrain from any legal action against us regarding your Contributions.

\n\nWe have the right, in our sole and absolute discretion, (1) to edit redact, or otherwise change any Contributions; (2) to recategorize any Contributions to place them in more appropriate locations in the Licensed Application; and (3) to pre-screen or delete any Contributions at any time and for any reason, without notice. We have no obligation to monitor your Contributions.

\n\n8. LIABILITY
\n8.1 Licensors responsibility in the case of violation of obligations and tort shall be limited to intent and gross negligence. Only in case Ota breach of essential contractual duties (cardinal obligations), Licensor shall also be liable in case of slight negligence. In any case, liability shall be limited to the foreseeable, contractually typical damages. The limitation mentioned above does not apply to injuries to lite, limb, or health.
\n8.2 Licensor takes no accountability or responsibility for any damages caused due to a breach of duties according to Section 2 of this License Agreement To avoid data loss, You are required to make use of backup functions of the Licensed Application to the extent allowed by applicable third-party terms and conditions of use. You are aware that in case of alterations or manipulations of the Licensed Application, You will not have access to the Licensed Application.

\n\n9. WARRANTY
\n9.1 Licensor warrants that the Licensed Application is tree of spyware, trojan horses, viruses, or any other malware at the time of Your download. Licensor warrants that the Licensed Application works as described in the user documentation.
\n9.2 No warranty is provided for the Licensed Application that is not executable on the device, that has been unauthorisedly modified, handled inappropriately or culpably, combined, or installed with inappropriate hardware or software, used with inappropriate accessories, regardless of it by Yourself or by third parties, or it there are any other reasons outside of Drivme Co., Ltd.’s sphere of influence that affect the executability of the Licensed Application.
\n9.3 You are required to inspect the Licensed Application immediately after installing it and notify Drivme Co., Ltd. about issues discovered without delay by email provided in Product Claims. The detect report will be taken into consideration and further investigated if it has been emailed within a period of ninety (90) days after discovery.
\n9.4 It we confirm that the Licensed Application is detective, Drivme Co., Ltd reserves a choice to remedy the situation either by means of solving the detect or substitute deliver.
\n9.5 In the event of any failure of the Licensed Application to conform to any applicable warranty, You may notify the Services Store Operator, and Your Licensed Application purchase price will be refunded to You. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, the Services Store Operator will have no other warranty obligation whatsoever with respect to the Licensed Application, and any other losses, claims, damages, liabilities, expenses, and costs attributable to any negligence to adhere to any warranty.
\n9.6 It the user is an entrepreneur, any claim based on faults expires after a statutory period of limitation amounting to twelve (12) months after the Licensed Application was made available to the user. The statutory periods of limitation given by law apply for users who are consumers.

\n\n10. PRODUCT CLAIMS
\nDrivme Co., Ltd and the End-User acknowledge that Drivme Co., Ltd, and not the Services, is responsible for addressing any claims of the End- user or any third party relating to the Licensed Application or the End-user\'s possession and/or use of that Licensed Application, including, but not limited to:
\n• product liability claims;
\n• any claim that the Licensed Application tails to conform to any applicable legal or regulatory requirement; and
\n• claims arising under consumer protection, privacy, or similar legislation.

\n\n11. LEGAL COMPLIANCE
\nYou represent and warrant that You are not located in a country that is subject to a US Government embargo, or that has been designated by the LIS Government as a \'terrorist supporting\' country; and that You are not listed on any LIS Government list of prohibited or restricted parties.

\n\n12. TERMINATION
\nThe License is valid until terminated by Drivme Co., Ltd or by You. Your rights under this License will terminate automatically and without notice from Drivme Co., Ltd if You tail to adhere to any term(s) of this License_ upon License termination, You shall stop all use of the Licensed Application, and destroy all copies, full or partial, of the Licensed Application

\n\n13. THIRD-PARTY TERMS OF AGREEMENTS AND BENEFICIARY
\nDrivme Co., Ltd. represents and warrants that Drivme Co., Ltd. will comply with applicable third-party terms of agreement when using Licensed Application.

\n\nIn Accordance with Section 9 of the \'Instructions for Minimum Terms of Developers End-user License Agreement\', Google\'s subsidiaries shall be third-party beneficiaries of this End User License Agreement and — upon Your acceptance of the terms and conditions of this License Agreement, Google will have the right (and will be deemed to have accepted the right) to enforce this End User License Agreement against You as a third-party beneficiary thereof.

\n\n14. INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS
\nDrivme Co., Ltd. and the End-User acknowledge that in the event of any third-party claim that the Licensed Application or the End-Users possession and use of that Licensed Application infringes on the third party\'s intellectual property rights, Drivme Co., Ltd., and not the Services, will be solely responsible for the investigation, defence, settlement, and discharge or any such intellectual property infringement claims.

\n\n15. APPLICABLE LAW
\nThis License Agreement is governed by the laws of Malaysia excluding its conflicts of law rules.

\n\n16. MISCELLANEOUS
\n16.1 It any of the terms of this agreement should be or become invalid, the validity of the remaining provisions shall not be affected. Invalid terms will be replaced by valid ones formulated in a way that will achieve the primary purpose
\n16.2 Collateral agreements, changes and amendments are only valid if laid down in writing. The preceding clause can only be waived in writing.

\n\n17. CONTACT US
\nFor general inquiries, complaints, questions, or claims concerning the Licensed Application, please contact:
\nDrivme Co., Ltd
\n123, Anywhere Road
\nAny City, Penang 123456
\nMalaysia
\nsupport@drivme.com</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy">Last updated August 22, 2022

\n\nDrivme (\"we\", \"our\", or \"us\") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how your personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by Drivme.

\n\nThis Privacy Policy applies to our application named Drivme, and its associated subdomains (collectively, our \"Service\"). By accessing or using our Service, you signify that you have read, understood, and agree to our collection, storage, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service.

\n\nDefinitions and key terms
\nTo help explain things as clearly as possible in this Privacy Policy, every time any of these terms are referenced, are strictly defined as:
\n• Cookie: small amount of data generated by a website and saved by your web browser. It is used to identify your browser, provide analytics, remember information about you such as your language preference or login
\n• Company: when this policy mentions \"Company\", \"we\", \"us\", or \"our\" it refers to Drivme Co., Ltd., 123, Anywhere Road, 123456 Any City, Penang, Malaysia that is responsible for your information under this Privacy Policy.
\n• Country: where Drivme or the owners/founders of Drivme are based, in this case is Malaysia.
\n• Customer: refers to the company, organization or person that signs up to use the Drivme Service to manage the relationships with your consumers or service users.
\n• Device: any internet connected device such as a phone, tablet, computer, or any other device that can be used to visit Drivme and use the services.
\n• IP address: Every device connected to the Internet is assigned a number known as an Internet protocol (IP) address. These numbers are usually assigned in geographic blocks. An IP address can often be used to identify the location from which a device is connecting to the Internet.
\n• Personnel: refers to those individuals who are employed by Drivme or are under contract to perform a service on behalf of one of the parties.
\n• Personal Data: any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.
\n• Service: refers to the service provided by Drivme as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this platform.
\n• Third-party service: refers to advertisers, contest sponsors, promotional and marketing partners, and others who provide our content or whose products or services we think may interest you.
\n• Website: Drivme\'s site, which can be accessed via this URL:
\n• You: a person or entity that is registered with Drivme to use the Services.

\n\nTABLE OF CONTENTS
\n1. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
\n2. HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?
\n3. WHEN DO WE USE CUSTOMER INFORMATION FROM THIRD PARTIES?
\n4. DO WE SHARE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT WITH THIRD PARTIES?
\n5. WHERE AND WHEN IS INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM CUSTOMERS AND END USERS?
\n6. HOW DO WE USE YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS?
\n7. COULD MY INFORMATION BE TRANSFERRED TO OTHER COUNTRIES?
\n8. IS THE INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH OUR SERVICE SECURE?
\n9. CAN I UPDATE OR CORRECT MY INFORMATION?
\n10. PERSONNEL
\n11. SALE OF BUSINESS
\n12. AFFILIATES
\n13. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?
\n14. HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?
\n15. GOVERNING LAW
\n16. YOUR CONSENT
\n17. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
\n18. COOKIES
\n19. PAYMENT DETAILS
\n20. KIDS\' PRIVACY
\n21. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
\n22. THIRD-PARTY SERVICES
\n23. TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES
\n24. INFORMATION ABOUT GENERAL DATA PROTECTION
\n25. WHAT IS GDPR?
\n26. WHAT IS PERSONAL DATA?
\n27. WHY IS GDPR IMPORTANT?
\n28. INDIVIDUAL DATA SUBJECT\'S RIGHTS - DATA ACCESS, PORTABILITY AND DELETION
\n29. CONTACT US

\n\n1. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
\nWe collect information from you when you visit our service, register, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, or fill out a form.
\n• Name / Username
\n• Phone Numbers
\n• Email Addresses
\n• Password

\n\nWe also collect information from mobile devices for a better user experience, although these features are completely optional:
\n• Location (GPS): Location data Location data helps to create an accurate representation of your interests, and this can be used to bring more targeted and relevant ads to potential customers.

\n\n2. HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?
\nAny of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
	\n· To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
	\n· To improve our service (we continually strive to improve our service offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
	\n· To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
	\n· To process transactions
	\n· To administer a contest, promotion, survey, or other site feature
	\n· To send periodic emails

\n\n3. WHEN DO WE USE CUSTOMER INFORMATION FROM THIRD PARTIES?
\nWe receive some information from the third parties when you contact us. For example, when you submit your email address to us to show interest in becoming our customer, we receive information from a third party that provides automated fraud detection services to us. We also occasionally collect information that is made publicly available on social media websites. You can control how much of your information social media websites make public by visiting these websites and changing your privacy settings.

\n\n4. DO WE SHARE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT WITH THIRD PARTIES?
\nWe may share the information that we collect, both personal and non-personal, with third parties such as advertisers, contest sponsors, promotional and marketing partners, and others who provide our content or whose products or services we think may interest you. We may also share it with our current and future affiliated companies and business partners, and if we are involved in a merger, asset sale or other business reorganization, we may also share or transfer your personal and non-personal information to our successors-in-interest.

\n\nWe may engage trusted third-party service providers to perform functions and provide services to us, such as hosting and maintaining our servers and our service, database storage and management, e-mail management, storage marketing, credit card processing, customer service and fulfilling orders for products and services you may purchase through our service. We will likely share your personal information, and possibly some non-personal information, with these third parties to enable them to perform these services for us and for you.

\n\nWe may share portions of our log file data, including IP addresses, for analytics purposes with third parties such as web analytics partners, application developers, and ad networks. If your IP address is shared, it may be used to estimate general location and other technographics such as connection speed, whether you have visited the service in a shared location, and type of device used to visit the service. They may aggregate information about our advertising and what you see on the service and then provide auditing, research and reporting for us and our advertisers.

\n\nWe may also disclose personal and non-personal information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in order to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect our rights and interests or those of a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to otherwise comply with applicable court orders, laws, rules and regulations.

\n\n5. WHERE AND WHEN IS INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM CUSTOMERS AND END USERS?
\nWe will collect personal information that you submit to us. We may also receive personal information about you from third parties as described above.

\n\n6. HOW DO WE USE YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS?
\nBy submitting your email address on our service, you agree to receive emails from us. You can cancel your participation in any of these email lists at any time by clicking on the opt-out link or other unsubscribe option that is included in the respective email. We only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directly, or through a third party. We do not send unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you do. By submitting your email address, you also agree to allow us to use your email address for customer audience targeting on sites like Facebook, where we display custom advertising to specific people who have opted- in to receive communications from us. Email addresses submitted only through the order processing page will be used for the sole purpose of sending you information and updates pertaining to your order. If, however, you have provided the same email to us through another method, we may use it for any of the purposes stated in this Policy.

\n\nNote: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

\n\n7. COULD MY INFORMATION BE TRANSFERRED TO OTHER COUNTRIES?
\nWe are incorporated in Malaysia. Information collected via our website, through direct interactions with you, or from use of our help services may be transferred from time to time to our offices or personnel, or to third parties, located throughout the world, and may be viewed and hosted anywhere in the world, including countries that may not have laws of general applicability regulating the use and transfer of such data. To the fullest extent allowed by applicable law, by using any of the above, you voluntarily consent to the trans- border transfer and hosting of such information.

\n\n8. IS THE INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH OUR SERVICE SECURE?
\nWe take precautions to protect the security of your information. We have physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help safeguard, prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use your information. However, neither people nor security systems are fool proof, including encryption systems. In addition, people can commit intentional crimes, make mistakes, or fail to follow policies. Therefore, while we use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If applicable law imposes any non-disclaimable duty to protect your personal information, you agree that intentional misconduct will be the standards used to measure our compliance with that duty.

\n\n9. CAN I UPDATE OR CORRECT MY INFORMATION?
\nThe rights you must request updates or corrections to the information we collect depend on your relationship with us. Personnel may update or correct their information as detailed in our internal company employment policies. Customers have the right to request the restriction of certain uses and disclosures of personally identifiable information as follows. You can contact us to (1) update or correct your personally identifiable information, (2) change your preferences with respect to communications and other information you receive from us, or (3) delete the personally identifiable information maintained about you on our systems (subject to the following paragraph), by cancelling your account. Such updates, corrections, changes, and deletions will have no effect on other information that we maintain, or information that we have provided to third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy prior to such update, correction, change or deletion. To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for always maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information. You should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove each record of the information you have provided to us from our system. The need to back up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate. Promptly after receiving your request, all personal information stored in databases we actively use, and other readily searchable media will be updated, corrected, changed, or deleted, as appropriate, as soon as and to the extent reasonably and technically practicable. If you are an end user and wish to update, delete, or receive any information we have about you, you may do so by contacting the organization of which you are a customer.

\n\n10. PERSONNEL
\nIf you are one of our workers or applicants, we collect information you voluntarily provide to us. We use the information collected for Human Resources purposes to administer benefits to workers and screen applicants. You may contact us to (1) update or correct your information, (2) change your preferences with respect to communications and other information you receive from us, or (3) receive a record of the information we have relating to you. Such updates, corrections, changes, and deletions will have no effect on other information that we maintain, or information that we have provided to third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy prior to such update, correction, change or deletion.

\n\n11. SALE OF BUSINESS
\nWe reserve the right to transfer information to a third party in the event of a sale, merger or other transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of us or any of its Corporate Affiliates (as defined herein), or that portion of us or any of its Corporate Affiliates to which the Service relates, or in the event that we discontinue our business or file a petition or have filed against us a petition in bankruptcy, reorganization or similar proceeding, provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

\n\n12. AFFILIATES
\nWe may disclose information (including personal information) about you to our Corporate Affiliates. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, \"Corporate Affiliate\" means any person or entity which directly or indirectly controls, is controlled by or is under common control with us, whether by ownership or otherwise. Any information relating to you that we provide to our Corporate Affiliates will be treated by those Corporate Affiliates in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

\n\n13. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?
\nWe keep your information only so long as we need it to provide service to you and fulfil the purposes described in this policy. This is also the case for anyone that we share your information with and who carries out services on our behalf. When we no longer need to use your information and there is no need for us to keep it to comply with our legal or regulatory obligations, we\'ll either remove it from our systems or depersonalize it so that we can\'t identify you.

\n\n14. HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?
\nWe implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) is never kept on file. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the absolute security of any information you transmit to us or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by a breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

\n\n15. GOVERNING LAW
\nThe laws of Malaysia, excluding its conflicts of law rules, shall govern this Agreement and your use of our service. Your use of our service may also be subject to other local, state, national, or international laws.

\n\n16. YOUR CONSENT
\nBy using our service, registering an account, or making a purchase, you consent to this Privacy Policy.

\n\n17. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
\nThis Privacy Policy applies only to the Services. The Services may contain links to other websites not operated or controlled by us. We are not responsible for the content, accuracy or opinions expressed in such websites, and such websites are not investigated, monitored, or checked for accuracy or completeness by us. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Services to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our platform, is subject to that website\'s own rules and policies. Such third parties may use their own cookies or other methods to collect information about you.

\n\n18. COOKIES
\nWe use \"Cookies\" to identify the areas of our website that you have visited. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our website. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our website correctly or at all. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.

\n\n19. PAYMENT DETAILS
\nIn respect to any credit card or other payment processing details you have provided us, we commit that this confidential information will be stored in the most secure manner possible.

\n\n20. KIDS\' PRIVACY
\nWe do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If You are a parent or guardian and You are aware that Your child has provided Us with Personal Data, please contact Us. If We become aware that We have collected Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, We take steps to remove that information from our servers.

\n\n21. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
\nIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

\n\n22. THIRD-PARTY SERVICES
\nWe may display, include, or make available third-party content (including data, information, applications, and other products services) or provide links to third-party websites or services (\"Third- Party Services\").

\n\nYou acknowledge and agree that we shall not be responsible for any Third-Party Services, including their accuracy, completeness, timeliness, validity, copyright compliance, legality, decency, quality, or any other aspect thereof. We do not assume and shall not have any liability or responsibility to you or any other person or entity for any Third- Party Services.

\n\nThird-Party Services and links thereto are provided solely as a convenience to you, and you access and use them entirely at your own risk and subject to such third parties\' terms and conditions.

\n\n23. TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES
\nGoogle Maps APIs
\nGoogle Maps API is a robust tool that can be used to create a custom map, a searchable map, check-in functions, display live data synching with location, plan routes, or create a mashup just to name a few.
\nGoogle Maps API may collect information from You and from Your Device for security purposes.
\nGoogle Maps API collects information that is held in accordance with its Privacy Policy.

\n\n24. INFORMATION ABOUT GENERAL DATA PROTECTION
\nRegulation (GDPR) We may be collecting and using information from you if you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), and in this section of our Privacy Policy we are going to explain exactly how and why this data is collected, and how we maintain this data under protection from being replicated or used in the wrong way.

\n\n25. WHAT IS GDPR?
\nGDPR is an EU-wide privacy and data protection law that regulates how EU residents\' data is protected by companies and enhances the control the EU residents have, over their personal data.

\n\n26. WHAT IS PERSONAL DATA?
\nAny data that relates to an identifiable or identified individual. GDPR covers a broad spectrum of information that could be used on its own, or in combination with other pieces of information, to identify a person. Personal data extends beyond a person\'s name or email address. Some examples include financial information, political opinions, genetic data, biometric data, IP addresses, physical address, sexual orientation, and ethnicity. The Data Protection Principles include requirements such as:
\n• Personal data collected must be processed in a fair, legal, and transparent way and should only be used in a way that a person would reasonably expect.
\n• Personal data should only be collected to fulfil a specific purpose and it should only be used for that purpose. Organizations must specify why they need the personal data when they collect it.
\n• Personal data should be held no longer than necessary to fulfil its purpose. They can also request a copy of their data, and that their data be updated, deleted, restricted, or moved to another organization.

\n\n27. WHY IS GDPR IMPORTANT?
\nGDPR adds some new requirements regarding how companies should protect individuals\' personal data that they collect and process. It also raises the stakes for compliance by increasing enforcement and imposing greater fines for breach. Beyond these facts it\'s simply the right thing to do. At Help Scout we strongly believe that your data privacy is very important, and we already have solid security and privacy practices in place that go beyond the requirements of this new regulation.

\n\n28. INDIVIDUAL DATA SUBJECT\'S RIGHTS - DATA ACCESS, PORTABILITY AND DELETION
\nWe are committed to helping our customers meet the data subject rights requirements of GDPR. Drivme processes or stores all personal data in fully vetted, DPA compliant vendors. We do store all conversation and personal data for up to 6 years unless your account is deleted. In which case, we dispose of all data in accordance with our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, but we will not hold it longer than 60 days.

\n\nWe are aware that if you are working with EU customers, you need to be able to provide them with the ability to access, update, retrieve and remove personal data. We got you! We\'ve been set up as self-service from the start and have always given you access to your data and your customers data. Our customer support team is here for you to answer any questions you might have about working with the API.

\n\n29. CONTACT US
\nFor general inquiries, complaints, questions, or claims concerning the Privacy Policy, please contact:
\nDrivme Co., Ltd .
\n123, Anywhere Road
\nAny City, Penang 123456
\nMalaysia
\nsupport@drivme.com</string>
</resources>